https://www.aceplumbing.com/privacy-policy/

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for (website address). This privacy
policy applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Contact FormsIn order to use this website, a user may complete a contact form. A user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest.
CookiesWe use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 915-455-4548 or via email.
Search
Recent Posts
Plumber Vs Plumbing Contractor: What’s the Difference in Sacramento?
Sacramento Home Improvements as Tax Deductions?
November 2020  (6)
October 2020  (6)
July 2020  (6)
June 2020  (6)
May 2020  (6)
February 2020  (6)
December 2019  (6)
November 2019  (6)
October 2019  (6)
September 2019  (6)
August 2019  (6)
June 2019  (6)
May 2019  (5)
April 2019  (7)
March 2019  (2)
February 2019  (4)
January 2019  (4)
December 2018  (5)
November 2018  (2)
October 2018  (6)
September 2018  (3)
August 2018  (3)
July 2018  (4)
June 2018  (2)
May 2018  (2)
April 2018  (4)
March 2018  (5)
February 2018  (6)
January 2018  (6)
December 2017  (6)
November 2017  (21)
October 2017  (1)
September 2017  (2)
August 2017  (1)
July 2017  (7)
June 2017  (6)
May 2017  (6)
April 2017  (6)
March 2017  (6)
February 2017  (6)
January 2017  (11)
December 2016  (2)
October 2016  (9)
September 2016  (1)
July 2016  (5)
May 2016  (3)
March 2016  (16)
February 2016  (1)
August 2013  (2)
July 2013  (1)
June 2013  (1)
May 2013  (4)
April 2013  (3)
March 2013  (2)
February 2013  (2)
January 2013  (4)
December 2012  (4)
November 2012  (1)
October 2012  (1)
September 2012  (3)
August 2012  (3)
July 2012  (3)
June 2012  (2)
